eatingbirdfood.com 2017-07-09

# Privacy Policy - Eating Bird Food

Eating Bird Food is firmly committed to maintaining the privacy and protection of your personal information. This Privacy Policy outlines our efforts to maintain your privacy.

 **Why Did You Receive An Email From Us?**

You receive mailings from eatingbirdfood.com for one of two reasons:

  * Your email address has been provided to us as someone who has expressly shared this address for the purpose of receiving information (blog posts, comments, etc.) in the future (“opt-in”);
  * You left a comment and Eating Bird Food responded

We respect your time and attention by controlling the content and frequency of our mailings.

 **How Your Privacy Is Protected**

Eating Bird Food uses security measures to protect against the loss, misuse and alteration of data you have provided to us.

 **Usage and Sharing**

We do not sell, share, or rent individual personal information with anyone without your advance written permission or unless ordered by a court of law.

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). For example, Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We respond to subpoenas, court orders, or legal process, or to establish or exercise our legal rights or defend against legal claims. Information submitted to us is only available to employees managing this information, for purposes of contacting you or sending you emails based on your request for information and to contracted service providers for purposes of providing services relating to our communications with you. We may transfer the information that you have provided to us if 101cookbooks.com is acquired by or merged with another company. In this event, 101cookbooks.com will notify you before information about you is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

 **How Can You Stop Receiving Email From Eating Bird Food?**

Each email sent contains an automated way for you to stop receiving email messages from Eating Bird Food in the future. If you would like to do this—to “opt-out” —simply follow the links at the bottom of every email message.  
**  
Privacy Policy Changes**

This policy was last updated on October 6, 2012.
